<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Luke Hines : Bottle of Code</title>
    <link>https://zackslash.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Luke Hines : Bottle of Code</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zackslash.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Redaction can still leak data</title>
      <link>https://zackslash.github.io/posts/redaction-can-still-leak-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zackslash.github.io/posts/redaction-can-still-leak-data/</guid>
      <description>This documents my discovery of a leaky redaction technique used in the payment platform &amp;lsquo;Payeer&amp;rsquo;. I think it is a good demonstration of how redaction can be used but still not meet its intent.
Someone once asked me what I knew about the payment provider ‘Payeer’ as an alternative to Paypal, this prompted me to do a small bit of research and check them out. One thing that caught my eye was a feature on the marketing front page of payeer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MIDI Translation</title>
      <link>https://zackslash.github.io/posts/midi-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zackslash.github.io/posts/midi-translation/</guid>
      <description>Download the Pro2Addict tool: Mac – Windows – Linux – Source Code
Keep reading for some insight into the solution.
MIDI files are the universal standard for music data such as musical notes, when they are played and how long each note is held. They work great for the majority of instruments that follow a standard notation; however there are some inconsistencies when interpreting music for percussion instruments.
I encountered these inconsistencies when trying to move a drum composition from Guitar Pro 6 into Addictive Drums 2; the way in which drum notes are recorded in the MIDI format means that one program may interpret them completely differently to another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monsoon power monitoring hardware and iPhone</title>
      <link>https://zackslash.github.io/posts/monsoon-power-monitor-hardware-and-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zackslash.github.io/posts/monsoon-power-monitor-hardware-and-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Note: This post was originally written in 2015 and i&amp;rsquo;ve recieved great sucess stories from numerous people of whom it has helped. I&amp;rsquo;ve had reports of this technique working for many of the later iPhone models and even the Apple watch! This post was also used as a reference in the book High Performance iOS Apps. What follows is the original article.
Sometimes you have to dig deep in search of optimization; one such place is power usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding files to Xcode projects from CLI</title>
      <link>https://zackslash.github.io/posts/xcode-add-files-from-command-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zackslash.github.io/posts/xcode-add-files-from-command-line/</guid>
      <description>NOTE!: It&amp;rsquo;s now the year 2020 and I believe this technique no longer works in the latest versions of xcode. I have archived the github repo. I&amp;rsquo;ve left everything public so the information still exists. What follows is my original article from 2014&amp;hellip;
There have been times when building xcode projects from terminal has been very convenient, i’ve also done it in a lot of scripts, however there is a drawback to this technique and I hope to solve it in this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom GPS data in the iOS simulator</title>
      <link>https://zackslash.github.io/posts/custom-gps-data-in-the-ios-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zackslash.github.io/posts/custom-gps-data-in-the-ios-simulator/</guid>
      <description>If you want to simulate GPS data in the iOS simulator you have two choices, Apple&amp;rsquo;s ‘real’ data (City run, freeway drive ect) or you can choose a single lat,long to simulate being in a static location, but… what if we want to simulate our own motorcycle ride or boat journey and work with ‘real’ GPS data in the simulator?
My open source tool ‘XJourney‘ (Available HERE) achieves just this. Using XJourney you can put your own GPS data into the iOS simulator to simulate a full GPS Journey just like Apple’s own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packaging a distributable Object-C library</title>
      <link>https://zackslash.github.io/posts/distributable-ios-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zackslash.github.io/posts/distributable-ios-framework/</guid>
      <description>It’s coming to the end of a project and the final deliverable will be a library for iOS. I have seen a lot of people distribute these frameworks as a .zip with the prebuilt .a, separate .h files and resources, but there is a cleaner, friendlier way, that is to package everything into a .framework &amp;amp; .bundle then distribute these as a .dmg.
We then move from giving customers a .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>